Dead is the day
The night
is full of
tra ge dy
The day
is dead
Darkness consumes the earth, \
octurnal empires awake
The sun nolonger heats,
the lands and the seas
Demons rising from their pits,
plunging the earth into abyss
No light shall shine  the sun  eclipsed,
forever redeemed
Howling winds
like piercing blades,
quick death
now awaits
The night is here,
dead is the day
The reaper has come...
to take you below
He’ll take you below
Down below
The Night is now
eternaly
The day
is dead
is black
Forever in
the dark
Howling winds
like piercing blades,
quick death
now awaits
The night is here,
dead is the day
The reaper
has come
Tonight
is full of
tra ge dy
The day
is dead
Darkness consumes the earth,
nocturnal empires awake
The sun nolonger heats,
the lands and the seas
Demons rising from their pits,
plunging the earth into abyss
No light shall shine  the sun  eclipsed,
forever redeemed
By pain and fear deformed,
feeble minds soon to break
the moon forever shines,
upon their graves
The King of night shall reign supreme,
destroying  global sanity
None shall live to be free
Darkness remains!